Mihaela Brodetchi

mihaelabrodetchi@gmail.com

0857455238

I am a third year Software Development student. I pride myself in my adaptability and attention to detail. My experience in customer facing roles has given me confidence in my interpersonal and client-facing skills. I have a keen interest in programming, specifically web programming and UI/UX. I am also passionate about the creative arts, including photography, digital, and traditional art. My time studying illustration has fuelled my interest in web development, UI/UX, and creative implementation of programming.

Work Experience

Sales Administrator

Michael Murphy Home Furnishing, Newbridge August 2020 to Present

- Receiving tickets from stores, which requests tasks to be carried out that cannot be done at store level. ie. Store credit, refunds, invoice edits, stock allocation.
- Identifying any system issues/bugs before they affect operations in the stores.
- Working closely with our warehouse, call centre, and sales staff to ensure the correct processing of invoices from all departments.
- Logging each store's requests and categorising them to identify if there are any stores that run into particular issues more often than others.

Receptionist

Michael Murphy Home Furnishing, Newbridge November 2019 to August 2020

- Main information hub of the building, directing both customers and staff in all queries and tasks, respectively.
- Working with SAP and TRC software at both staff and management level, and training staff on using these applications.
- Ensuring the payments taken in at all payment points in store accurately match the values being represented to the accounting department.
- Troubleshooting software issues and finding workarounds for system errors.

Sales Assistant

I-Connect, Whitewater, Newbridge July 2018 to November 2019

- Administrator work, ordering and transferring stock in company, processing customer support tickets, processing warranty requests.
- Troubleshooting devices (laptops, iPads, iPhones, and Apple watches) and providing relevant customer support.
- Wide range of product knowledge in order to best advise customers.
- Cash handling, bank deposits, lodging G4S deposits.

Sales Assistant

Cambridge Satchel Company, Kildare Village February 2018 to April 2018

- Adding new shipments to stock and writing off damaged goods.
- Personalised embossing done by hand using leather embossing machine.
- Arranging displays and restocking shelves with products.
- Customer interaction and assistance.
- Start and end of day duties, including clean up, banking, and a spreadsheet reporting the daily sales and intakes.

Sales Assistant

Vodafone Retail, Monread, Naas July 2017 to January 2018

- Troubleshoot issues, provide technical support and carry out minor fixes on phones, following up individual cases to ensure any problems are resolved.
- Carry out my duties in preparing the shop at the start and end of the day, such as cleaning, checking and ordering stock, checking cash.
- Inputting and processing applications for customers seeking broadband, TV, and bill-pay plans.
- Meet monthly targets by evaluating individual cases and upselling products based on customers' needs.

Education

Bachelor's in Software Development

IT Carlow - Carlow

September 2018 to Present

Higher National Diploma in Illustration in Illustration

Ballyfermot College of Further Education

2015 to 2017

Skills

- Fluent English, professional Romanian, beginner Russian.
- Adobe Suite: Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign.
- Microsoft Office Suite: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, and Access.
- HTML, CSS, Javascript.
- Linux/Unix, Debian, Ubuntu.
- Java(using Eclipse), currently studying C++ and Python.

Links

http://github.com/404UserNotFound

http://linkedin.com/in/mihaela-brodetchi